So, this is the presentation for Checkgrow, how to use the sales outreach, and everything
here starts with the company knowledge, but for the sales, the only thing we need to focus
really is on the ICP.
So the ideal customer profiles are here, what needs to be approved and managed, we can also
see in the table view, and then you can see here that those ICPs, when you open it, you
have a specific context that will supply the sales, for example, the most important here
besides of the keywords, company size, annual revenue, it's the target, right?
The target titles, the people, the job positions, so head of corporate development, the director
of M&A, so this will influence on how we are targeting people in LinkedIn-specific.
So after having that sorted out, we go to the outreach.
And in the outreach feature, we come here and the first thing we should do is to connect
our sales rep here, clicking this square, you're going to connect your LinkedIn account.
You can also do that coming here in integrations and clicking in LinkedIn, then you can connect
your LinkedIn account here in the same way.
After having the sales rep connected, you can go to the sales feature called Target.
In the target feature, you click in search in the top and you're going to see here the
selection of the ICPs which are built on the knowledge center.
So in that case, for example, if I select investment banking, you're going to have instant research
of this ICP.
What is related with the industry, the target of revenue, the market, the country, the region,
so those are companies that are related with this specific ICP.
The next step is to select the companies.
You can always open their website and they're LinkedIn here to understand better about the
company, but this is basically their revenue and their growth and their founding here.
You select the companies that you want to track and you come down and you click in track.
After clicking track, you can go here in the track function and here you're going to have
the list of the companies that we are tracking.
In the right side, you have the mission control, which are the ICPs that you want to get as
I score to understand what is the score of these companies related with each ICP and I will
show you where, as well, the assignments, people that are connected in the outreach already
with the LinkedIn integrate.
So having that here, we can do a few settings.
Clicking the tracker settings, you can again select the ICPs that you want to measure the
score on the tracking, as well clicking and avoid and add company or people that you want
to avoid in this tracking.
Let's say that you want to upload something here directly from your CRM and then all these
companies will be avoided and not tracked as well, not outreach.
Having these settings properly done, you can go through the companies that you are tracking
here, you can filter the companies by industry or by alignment, ICP and then you do the search.
In the company that you are tracking, you can have the right information to attack.
So that means you have the company shape that go from the revenue, the employees, the amount
of followers, the interest, the headquarters, the founded year, the social media and the
decision makers.
So these decision makers here, they are related with the ICP job positions, right?
You can go down and you're going to see the score related with the tracker settings.
So this specific company are good score, let's say 6 in the investment banking UK, but of
course they are low score on the automotive Germany.
This is a way that we can check the ICP scores according with the company goals, right?
If you keep going down, you're going to have the sales intelligence.
So for example, here in the best move, you can see that a good idea is to send a congratulations
to Nick's fees and Evie then because of their latest deals.
In the same way, you can have the markets team and understand why rooms fits, why the
company fits for them in the specific segment.
You hear in the bottom, you can have, for example, their latest news, their signals,
what happened in the last moves with them.
And you can also like a refresh year to unlock competitors that are related with this company.
But going up here, the most important is the decision makers.
So if you are not happy with these decision makers, you can click in positions and then
you're going to see all the positions that we are searching related with our ICPs, right?
So you can add extra positions for the specific industry and then we're going to be targeting
these industries all the time.
And you can find people in that company here in a specific job position.
So this is very important to customize.
Now after you have all the companies here tracked and you know which ones you want and
which ones you don't want according with the avoiding settings, you can sign people.
So you can come here and sign someone from your team and then all the targets that are
from this company will go to their outreach settings, which I'm going to show next.
Important here is that we have in the mission control, we have the auto-assign feature.
So you can go in the sales here, for example, if I click in Johannes, I can click in
the auto-assign and clicking the auto-assign, I can select the industries as well, the locations
and save it.
When I save it, all the companies that are from the specific settings of the auto-assign
in Johannes will be automatic sign to him here.
So you can see here that I can go in future and I can select Johannes and I can see
all the companies that Johannes are assigned here on the tracking settings.
Okay, what happened after having all this tracking, all these companies, all these assignments
on the target function?
You can go to the outreach function and the outreach function is where we have overview
of what is happening, right?
So in the outreach function, you have first of all the sales reps here.
If I open Johannes, this is his brain.
And this is where the sales team should have most of the work.
What should be done here?
In the right side, you have the target audiences where you can teach our brain with which industries
you are mostly relating, which regions and which I see this and this will not affect
the outreach, it will affect just how your brain are communicating.
You have the language, this will affect your brain and your outreach.
If you select a specific language, a specific language will be written.
If you click match target language, that means that the message and the comments will be written
according with the sales rep, the target language in the post or the profile.
In the bottom, you fix the personality here.
So you can always write something, for example, don't speak like that or like this.
And you send it.
And when you send that, it will be stored in your brain as well.
You can set up your style, you can add a new tone, you can choose the directness, the
formality, the land as well, the relationship approach, the avoidance, what you want to avoid
or not.
So having this personality set up, you can also in the left side, always teaching the
brain with learning.
You can tell him what you want, what you don't want, how to communicate, how to communicate
and all of that will be here.
You can see them here.
So this is the teaching that Johannes gave to the brain as well.
You can upload files in the knowledge files here.
You can always drop a file that you will literally see, you're going to offer knowledge that
can come from Claude or GPT or any LLM to teach in large scale what you want the brain to do.
In the middle, you have the message playground.
In the message playground, you have different message and different generations here that
you can like or dislike or you can change.
So the message playground is the most important space.
What should you do here is you should select what you want to train.
If you want to train a comment in their LinkedIn post, if you want to train the first message
or if you want to train the follow up message or reply, you're clicking post comment and
then you're going to train the comment.
If you want to, if you click in the first message, you're going to train the first message and
so on.
If you don't have a first message to train, you're just clicking generate and AI will
get your whole brain instructions, your complex, the context of the company and will generate
specific message for you to interact with.
So when you have the message, you should click on dislike and tell what you don't like and
why and or you should click like or you should edit and save or you should click in favor.
If you click in favor, this message will be signed as a good message, which can be used
to train the brain in further actions.
After training the brain, you're clicking targets.
Here you can see all the targets that are related with a specific sales rep.
This is coming from the target companies, specifically with the industries and the assignments of
this sales rep in the platform.
So what happened here is, this is the target mode, right?
First of all, this is disabled by standards, so nothing's happening when you first connect
here.
You can click in the settings here in the site and you're going to select if you want approval
process or if you want to send things automatically.
Let's start with approval process, right?
And here is the timing for the first message, the follow up message and what happened later.
So, having the settings here, you can also click in the automated connections.
You can select how many connections you want per day and you can also click in the warm
outreach message, which will send a message automatically for the targets.
But both settings here will only work according with the default settings that is if you want
to approve or if you want to send automatically.
What happened after you activated that and you can see that Johannes had this activated
before, connections will be sent.
So you can open the target here and you're going to see the history in the bottom.
We send a connection here on 8 September, the connection was requested.
In a few days, we keep checking if the connection was accepted or not.
And then on the 12 September, the target accepted the connection.
What our model do is, it will research the recent posts of this person and if the person
have a good post, it will write a comment for the post.
If there is no post recent, it will just write a warm up message.
You will write the warm up message, prepare the message and we will ask for your approval.
So how this approval works?
If you want to go individually in each person, you can just check the message, you can just
dislike and generate a new one or you can approve and the message is instantly sent to
the person.
But if you're clicking the top on outreach, you can come here every day and that's the
main work to be done on the day to day basis.
You're clicking outreach and you just approve, dislike or edit and send the message.
So here are all the comments and all the message that you can approve to send for those leads
in the day to day basis.
That means that it's much easier for you to just come here and approving the message and
disliking and feeding the message and improving your brain knowledge at the same time.
You are collecting results and targeting leads every day.
So that's the basic idea, the basic idea of how the system works.
You can always click in Salesforce and check the whole force of the team here and right now
we have 2,409 targets assigned.
That means that we can just come to each sales rep and just come to their outreach and approve
the message and outreach those leads instantly without needing to open LinkedIn the right
send thing cloud, go back to the link and you can just write everything here in one
single time.
The biggest advantage is with time, we are teaching the brain and the brain will get better
and better to outreach until you can go to your settings in the target and you can change
to send automatically.
When you change to send automatically, you don't need to approve the message that more
everything is being out reached automatically with our targets.